#### Contact

aliwebdev3986@proton.me

www.linkedin.com/in/aliraza5490 (LinkedIn) aliwebdev.tech (Portfolio) github.com/aliraza5490 (Other)

### Top Skills

MERN Stack TypeScript Next.js

### Certifications

**APIs and Microservices** 

Crash Course on Python

Meta Front-End Developer Specialization

Front End Libraries

Javascript Algorithms and Data structures

# Ali raza

MERN Stack Web Developer | JavaScript | React | Node JS | MongoDB | Next JS

Multan, Punjab, Pakistan

## Summary

Hi there - I'm Ali, a full-stack web developer with expertise in JavaScript - React, and Node JS. I'm also familiar with TypeScript, Git, AJAX, Zustand, React-Query, Styled Components, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, and many other libraries. I can create responsive, fast, user-friendly SPA(Single Page Application) and landing page websites.

## Experience

Freelance
MERN stack Developer
July 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Tecudia
Back End Developer
May 2023 - July 2023 (3 months)
Remote

## Education

Muhammad Nawaz Sharif University of Engineering & Technology, Multan

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (August 2020 - August 2024)

Rise college, Multan

Associate's degree, Computer Science · (October 2018 - October 2020)

Garrison Grammar Higher Secondary School, Multan High School Diploma, Computer Science (July 2016 - July 2018)